<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<T3locallang>
	<meta type="array">
		<description>CSH labels for FlexForm fields</description>
		<type>CSH</type>
		<csh_table></csh_table>
		<fileId>EXT:toctoc_comments/pi1/locallang_csh.xml</fileId>
		<labelContext type="array">
		</labelContext>
	</meta>
	<data type="array">
		<languageKey index="default" type="array">
			<label index=".alttitle">toctoc_comments plugin configuration options</label>
			<label index="_.image">EXT:toctoc_comments/ext_icon.gif</label>
			<label index=".image_descr">Plugin options serve to overwrite the options set in general or page Typoscript.
Here, in the plugin itself - just make the exceptions work.</label>
			<label index="code.description">Defines operation mode of the plugin</label>
			<label index="code.details">&quot;Comment listing&quot; mode shows list of comments. &quot;Comment form&quot; mode shows form to enter comments.</label>
			<label index="externalPrefix.description">Defines a parameter in URL that will trigger comments displaying for records</label>
			<label index="externalPrefix.details">Defines a parameter in URL that will trigger comments displaying. Typically it is a parameter that defines a single view. For example, tt_news extension uses tx_ttnews[tt_news] as a parameter to define single item to show. Therefore external prefix is tx_ttnews in this case.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; To comment on content elements, the &quot;pages&quot; prefix is set automatically in background, you can leave the field blank.</label>
			<label index="storagePid.description">Defines where to store comment records</label>
			<label index="commentsPerPage.description">Defines how many comments to show</label>
			<label index="closeCommentsAfter.description">Defines a period after which commenting is closed</label>
			<label index="closeCommentsAfter.details">Period is defined by an integer number followed by suffix. Suffix can be h, m, y or d (meaning hours, months, years or days respectively). Example: 5d (means close commenting after 5 days). If empty, comments can be added at any moment.</label>
			<label index="requireApproval.description">Comments need be approved by moderator</label>
			<label index="requireApproval.details">If checked, every message will require to be approved by moderator. Moderator will receive an e-mail with comment content and links to approve or delete comment.</label>
			<label index="considerReferer.description">If checked, comments will not be approved unless referer matches current site</label>
			<label index="considerReferer.details">It is not safe to use this option because many browsers are not reliable in sending referer (and they are not really required to). Also many firewalls block this field. Use only if you are really paranoid about it.</label>
			<label index="useCaptcha.description">Require captcha to be submitted together with comment.</label>
			<label index="useCaptcha.image_descr">Example of captcha in the comment form</label>
			<label index="notificationEmail.description">Defines the e-mail address to which notifications about new unapproved comments are sent.</label>
			<label index="fromEmail.description">Defines the e-mail address from which e-mails are sent.</label>
			<label index="useWebpagePreview.description">Use Attachment Feature Webpagepreview</label>
			<label index="useWebpagePreview.details">if the Attachment feature Webpagepreview is enabled, then webpagepreviews are shown and users can generate new previews.</label>
			<label index="userStats.description">Create and maintain userstatistics</label>
			<label index="userStats.details">Check this option if you want to create statictis for each user leaving comments or making ratings. Slower, but better control.</label>
			<label index="useSharing.description">Use of Share-Links</label>
			<label index="useSharing.details">Use of Share-Links for social networks like Facebook, Google and Twitter</label>
			<label index="dontUseSharingFacebook.description">Share-Link for Facebook is suppressed</label>
			<label index="dontUseSharingFacebook.details">Use of Share-Link for Facebook is suppressed. Similar options exist for other social networks</label>
			<label index="commentingClosed.description">Stop Commenting</label>
			<label index="commentingClosed.details">Commenting can be totally suppressed, 0 (default) or 1</label>
			<label index="ratingsOnly.description">Enable only ratings</label>
			<label index="ratingsOnly.details">Enable ratings only just displays the rating component of the plugin</label>
			<label index="enableRatings.description">Enable ratings</label>
			<label index="enableRatings.details">Enables web site visitors to rate comments or records. Notice that ratings change is only available if comments are not closed for the item. When comments are closed, ratings automatically become read-only</label>
			<label index="useVotes.description">Shows voting</label>
			<label index="useVotes.details">Shows the rating stars and enables voting, if checked.</label>
			<label index="useMyVote.description">Show vote of user</label>
			<label index="useMyVote.details">Shows the vote of the user</label>
			<label index="useLikeDislike.description">Show Like and Dislike</label>
			<label index="useLikeDislike.details">Show Like and Dislike Features, if checked both are active.</label>
			<label index="useDislike.description">Show Dislike Feature</label>
			<label index="useDislike.details">The show Dislike features makes only sense in connection with useLikeDislike.</label>
			<label index="useTopWebpagePreview.description">Select a Webpage preview</label>
			<label index="useTopWebpagePreview.details">Select a Webpage preview that has been created in the frontend and assign it to the plugin. The Webpagepreview will be shown at the top of the plugin. It can be used to illustrate the article people are commenting on.</label>
			<label index="useCaptcha.image">EXT:toctoc_comments/csh/captcha.png</label>
		</languageKey>
	</data>
	<orig_hash type="array">
	</orig_hash>
	<orig_text type="array">
	</orig_text>
</T3locallang>