<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<T3locallang>
	<meta type="array">
		<description>CSH for additional tt_content fields</description>
		<type>CSH</type>
		<csh_table>tt_content</csh_table>
		<fileId>EXT:toctoc_comments/pi1/locallang_cecsh.xml</fileId>
	</meta>
	<data type="array">
		<languageKey index="default" type="array">
			<label index=".alttitle">Comments and ratings</label>
			<label index="_.image">EXT:toctoccommentsce/ext_icon.gif</label>
			<label index=".image_descr">The options you can setup for commenting in a content element are sent to extension toctoc_comments.
Note that the basic configuration of toctoc_comments is responsible for all other aspects of the look and feel of the commenting feature.</label>
			<label index="tx_toctoccommentsce_pluginmode.description">Defines operation mode of the plugin</label>
			<label index="tx_toctoccommentsce_pluginmode.details">&quot;Normal&quot; mode for use of social network components, including commenting, reviews, ratings and sharing. 
The other operation modes show specific views on the data: 
&quot;Recent Comments&quot; displays a recent comments list. 
&quot;Top ratings&quot; displays top rated records. 
&quot;User Center&quot; displays all comments and ratings of a logged in user. 
&quot;Search comments&quot; displays a form for searching comments.</label>
			<label index="tx_toctoccommentsce_external_ref.description">Plugin to table map for linking records of other extensions to &quot;Comments and ratings&quot;</label>
			<label index="tx_toctoccommentsce_external_ref.details">The plugin to table map triggers specific records like News, Products or other records with associated comments, reviews or ratings. 
If you miss Plugin to table maps in your database you can let import a first set of them by toctoc_comments. 
Please refer to toctoc_comments extensions configuration in extension manager, option database.importDataprefixtotable</label>
			<label index="tx_toctoccommentsce_enable_comments.description">Enable Comments, reviews, ratings or sharing</label>
			<label index="tx_toctoccommentsce_enable_comments.details">Enable this adds after the content element Comments, reviews, ratings or sharing</label>
			<label index="tx_toctoccommentsce_with_comments.description">Comments or reviews</label>
			<label index="tx_toctoccommentsce_with_comments.details">Show comments or reviews (or none of both)</label>
			<label index="tx_toctoccommentsce_with_ratings.description">Enable ratings</label>
			<label index="tx_toctoccommentsce_with_ratings.details">Enables web site visitors to rate comments or records.</label>
			<label index="tx_toctoccommentsce_with_sharing.description">Enable sharing</label>
			<label index="tx_toctoccommentsce_with_sharing.details">Enables sharing for social networks like Facebook, Google and Twitter</label>
			<label index="tx_toctoccommentsce_msg.description">Donation message</label>
			<label index="tx_toctoccommentsce_msg.details">This message either displays a link for you to make a donation for this wonderful software, or if you did, it displays a honourable donor message.</label>
		</languageKey>
	</data>
	<orig_hash type="array">
	</orig_hash>
	<orig_text type="array">
	</orig_text>
</T3locallang>